<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Henry Yeh&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://henryyeh.cc/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Henry Yeh&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 03:48:01 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://henryyeh.cc/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://henryyeh.cc/page/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 03:48:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://henryyeh.cc/page/projects/</guid>
      <description>FSE Emergency Social Network Emergency Social Network is a chat room based web application for citizen to exchange information during covid-19. This project contains several high-level requirements: Join Community, Login-Logout, Chat Publicly/Privately, Post Announcement, Share Status, Search Information, Administer User Profile, Health Report Generator, Covid-19 Map/Article Inventory/Supplies. And the following tech stacks are used:
web UI frontend: PUG(HTML)/CSS with bootstrap, jquery backend: node.js database: mongoDB unit-test framework: jest And this application is deployed on heroku with CircleCI</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://henryyeh.cc/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 17:51:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://henryyeh.cc/page/about/</guid>
      <description>About Henry My name is 葉瀚允 in Chinese and the translation is Han-Yun Yeh. You can just call me Henry.
I am a software engineer majoring in signal processing, especially speech and audio processing. Besides, I have experience with frontend, backend, DevOps, firmware development and the whole software engineering practices including CI/CD and testing. Now I am MS student in software engineering at CMU-SV.
With strong programming and mathematical knowledge of machine learning, 1 year of embedded programming experience and web development experience, I am open to positions related to audio/speech processing, general software design or web development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
